# Devansh Wadhwa

Cyber Security Researcher.

I have invested last 4 years learning and working in multiple disciplines like Cyber-Security, Digital Forensics, IOT, Robotics to Web Development. I am a self learner and I have practical exposure of implementing these skills via various projects and internships. I am currently looking for opportunities that can help me grow and give me space to show my skills and capabilities in cybersecurity.

w.devansh1337@gmail.com

8700882265

DELHI, INDIA

in linkedin.com/in/devanshw

#### **EDUCATION**

### Certified Ethical Hacker

**EC-Council** 

04/2021 - 04/2024

## **Computer Hacking Forensic Investigator**

**EC-Council** 

01/2021 - 01/2024

### Bachelor of Technology, ECE

GGSIPU, Delhi

08/2017 - 07/2021

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Cyber and Strategic Risk - Intern

Deloitte India

07/2021 - Present

Delhi

# **Digital Forensic Examiner**

Systools Software Pvt Ltd.

01/2021 - 07/2021 Achievements/Tasks Delhi

- Search and Seizure of Digital Evidence With Income Tax Department.
- Digital Evidence Acquisition and Extraction.

### **Digital Forensics Intern** CvPAD, Delhi Police

09/2020 - 11/2020

Delhi

Achievements/Tasks

- Data Acquisition and Examination With criminal case standards.
- Digital Evidence Analysis.

### Cyber Security Intern

PAC Security

ONLINE

06/2020 - 09/2020 Achievements/Tasks

- Web Application testing:- manual and using the required tools such as Burp-Suite, NESSUS, OWASP-ZAP.
- Capture The Flag:- CTFs using the kali linux and tools such as metasploit.

### **Ethical Hacking Trainee**

Lucideus , Delhi

06/2018 - 09/2018

Delhi

Achievements/Tasks

- A Great Exposure to the field of Cybersecurity.
- Laid a Foundation stone, Gained a lot of skills.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Cyber Security

**Digital Forensics** 

Web Application Penetration Testing

Internet of Things

**Robotics and Drones** 

Front End Web development

### TOOLS AND OS

Windows, Mac OS, Linux, Android

Burp Suite, Metasploit, Wireshark

SqlMap, WpScan, Nessus, Owasp-Zap

Nmap, Hydra, Wfuzz, Hashcat

FTK Imager, UFED, MOBILEdit, X-ways

Arduino, Raspberry Pi, Esp8266

Html5, CSS3, Bootstrap4

### **PROJECTS**

#### WEB APPLICATION PENETRATION TESTING

Web Application PenetrationTesting at BUGCROWD, NCIIPC.

AI Based Vehicle detection and Traffic Management TOP 10 IN DELHI POLICE HACKATHON 2019

IOT BASED DEVICE FOR CRYOGENIC GRINDING

A project for SMART INDIA HACKATHON(HARDWARE-2019)

Various TYPES OF ROBOTS

Line Following, Robo War and soccer.

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### Hall Of Fame

Trip Advisor, Under Armour, Viator, Overstock, Socrata etc.

Final Round SMART INDIA HACKATHON (HARDWARE) 2019

Delhi Police Hackathon 2019 Top-10

Finished in Top 10

E-YANTRA 2019

Completed Stage 2

### Winner in various Tech Competitions.

AMITY UNIVERSITY, NOIDA; YMCA, FARIDABAD; NSUT, DELHI; USIT, DELHI, IGDTUW, DELHI; MAIT, DELHI; DTC, NOIDA etc.